docshare.com 2011-05-22

# Privacy Policy : DocShare Support

### Privacy Policy

Phil Mar-16 2009

Privacy Policy

**Version 1.0

1\. The Information Collected

**  
Registration on DocShare is optional but highly recommended for the most optimal experience. Upon registering we collect the following information:Information you provide- When signing up for a DocShare account we ask for personal information such as name, e-mail address, account password, and profile information.   

  * Cookie Information- When visiting DocShare, we may send one or more cookies which is commonly a small file containing a string of characters.  

  * Log information- When accessing DocShare, we may automatically record information sent by your browser.  

  * Submitted Content- Any personal information or document you disclose voluntarily becomes publicly available and can be viewed by others.  

**2\. Uses**  

  * DocShare uses the information you provide to better provide, operate, enhance the user experience and provide site services based on your information.  

  * DocShare collects personally identifiable user data to best to comply with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act.  

  * DocShare may use cookies to track browsing data to provide analytics and statistics based on that data.  

**3\. Publicly Available Information**  

  * You may choose to include personally identifiable information in your profile which may include your name, location, gender, picture, or other details, which will be viewable by others through your profile page.  

  * Your username will be used throughout the site when engaging in activities, at no time is your e-mail address exposed to other users.
  * Documents uploaded to the site may be distributed through other platforms and viewable by others if privacy options allow.  

4\. Third-Party Advertisers  
  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

5\. Additional Information

For additional information you may create a support ticket or write to:  
DocShare, LLC  
48 Wall Street, 11th Floor  
New York, NY 10005
